gv.com.sg 2019-10-19

# PrivacyPolicy - PrivacyPolicy

Your privacy is very important to us. We are committed to protecting the personal data that you disclose to us in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012. We will not disclose or sell your personal data to third parties for their marketing purposes without your express consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we collect, use and disclose your personal data.

We have prepared this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices on the collection, use and disclosure of personal data so that you can make informed decisions when using this website and any mobile applications that we may make available from time to time. By visiting this website or accessing any of our mobile applications, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access this website or any of our mobile applications. 

This Policy describes the information that we collect from you through this website or mobile applications and how the information would be used and disclosed.

In this Policy, “personal data” means any data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified (a) from that data; or (b) from that data and other information to which we have or are likely to have access, including data in our records as may be updated from time to time.

By using this website or any of the mobile applications, you will be deemed to have consented to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal data in accordance with this Policy. This Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Golden Village User Agreement. 

##### 1) INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

Our primary purpose in collecting personal data is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience when you use this website or any of the mobile applications. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal data about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

If you choose to use the services on this website or any of the mobile applications, we may require you to provide your contact and identity information and other personal information as indicated on the relevant forms. Where possible, we will indicate which fields are mandatory and which fields are optional. You will always have the option not to provide the information requested by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

In some situations, we may require you to provide financial information. We use your financial information, including credit card information, to verify the accuracy of your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services. 

##### 2) COOKIES 

We use cookies to automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the website or mobile application. Cookies are small pieces of information which are issued to your computer or mobile device when you visit this website or access or use a mobile application to store and track information about your use of this website or mobile application. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you visited prior to visiting this website, which URL you visited next, your computer browser information, and your IP address.

##### 3) OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use your personal data to facilitate the services you request. We also use your personal data with other information that we have collected from your current and past activities on the website or mobile application to: attend to your queries; troubleshoot technical problems; help promote safe online transactions; collect payments; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal data to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal data for errors, omissions and for accuracy. 

You agree that we may use your personal data for the aforesaid purposes, which are intended to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our online content, layout, and services. Such use of your personal data will enable us to constantly improve our website and mobile applications and tailor them to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the website or mobile application. 

You agree that we may also use your personal data to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the website or mobile application. 

##### 4) OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

As a matter of policy, we will not disclose or sell any of your personal data to third parties for their marketing purposes without your express consent. However, the following describes some of the ways information may be disclosed in the normal course of business to third parties in the provision of our services.

_Advertisers_. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal data and disclose such information as anonymised data to advertisers and other third parties for market analysis and consumer research. In such cases, we do not disclose to these third parties any information that could be used to identify you personally. In particular, we will not disclose sensitive information about you, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, to these third parties without your express consent. 

_Internal Service Providers for Our Operations_.We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you (e.g., search technology, discussion boards, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs, co-branded credit cards) and therefore we may provide some of your personal data directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality and data protection obligations and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced operation, unless you have expressly agreed or given your prior permission to them for other purposes. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all information that you provide to them and their use of the information will be strictly between you and the internal service provider. If you provide personal data directly to an internal service provider, then their use of the personal data that you provide to them will be governed by their applicable privacy policy. 

_Other Corporate Entities_. We share much of our data, including your personal data, with our related companies, subsidiaries and joint venture partners that are committed to serving your online transactions and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your personal data, they will be required to treat your personal data with at least the same level of protection as we treat your personal data.

##### 5) CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

Your information is stored on our servers located in Singapore. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal data against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. We treat personal data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. If you are aware of any security breach, please let us know as soon as possible. 

We have internal procedures in place requiring our employees and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any personal data held by us. 

However, as you can appreciate, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, so we cannot give an absolute assurance that the information you provide to us will be secure at all times, and we cannot be held responsible for any event arising from unauthorised access to your personal data that was not due to our default or negligence. We will not be held responsible for events arising from third parties gaining unauthorised access to your personal data that was beyond our control. 

##### 6) LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website, mobile applications and online purchase confirmation emails, may contain links to other websites, whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy policies of these other companies and we encourage you to consult their privacy policies before using their websites.

##### 7) CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to update this Policy from time to time as we expand our services. We will post a notice on our home page to inform you that an update has been made. Your use of the website or mobile application after this Policy has been updated will be deemed acceptance of the updated Policy.

##### 8) CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, you may send an email to our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@goldenvillage.com.sg](mailto:dpo@goldenvillage.com.sg). Alternatively, you may send your email to our Customer Service Department at [customersvc@goldenvillage.com.sg](mailto:customersvc@goldenvillage.com.sg)
